ideal808.com 2018-12-04

# Privacy Policy - IDeal808.com

Free Shipping On Singles 1st Class - $50 OR MORE | UPS $200 OR MORE    
*U.S. orders only. Orders must contain only Single Cards.

#### __FREE SHIPPING ON SINGLES

1st Class - $50 OR MORE | UPS $200 OR MORE*U.S. orders only. Orders must contain only Single Cards.

**Your Privacy**  
Ideal808is committed to protecting your privacy. We only use the information we collect about you to process orders and to provide support and upgrades for our products. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy.

 ** _What information do we collect? How do we use it?_**  
When you order, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number, and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status. When you enter a contest or other promotional feature, we may ask for your name, address, and e-mail address so we can administer the contest and notify winners. You agree to be added to our mailing list for future promotions and deals. When you order through our website, you are opting in to receive newsletters about promotions, coupons, and important company announcements. All emails are sent through ConstantContact and you may opt out if you wish to no longer receive newsletters from us or our MTG partners.

 _ **How does  **_

Ideal808 _ **protect customer information?**_  
We use a Secure Server for collecting personal and credit card information. The secure server layer (SSL) encrypts (scrambles) all of the information you enter before it is transmitted over the Internet and sent to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access.

 _ **What about "cookies"?**_  
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. We do not use cookies to collect or store any information about visitors or customers.

 _ **Will  **_

Ideal808 _ **disclose the information it collects to outside parties?**_  
Ideal808does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to companies not affiliated with Ideal808. Ideal808may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will not include personally identifying information.Ideal808may release account information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with law, (ii) enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements or (iii) protect the rights, property or safety of Ideal808, our users, or others.

 **In Summary**

Ideal808is committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect on the site to make shopping atIdeal808 .com as simple as possible and to enhance your overall shopping experience. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.

 **Your Consent**  
By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by

Ideal808 , Inc. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.Ideal808also provides links to affiliated sites. The privacy policies of these linked sites are the responsibility of the linked site and Ideal808has no control or influence over their policies. Please check the policies of each site you visit for specific information. Ideal808cannot be held liable for damage or misdoings of other sites linked or otherwise.

To assist us with our goal to achieve the highest quality of products and services, we use data from our interactions with you and other customers. Your privacy is a priority to us, and to ensure that your personal information is handled in a safe, secure, and responsible manner company policies are constantly reinforced by management. We have outlined this privacy policy below to inform you what kind of information we collect, how it is processed, with whom it may be shared, and how you may access some of the information you provide us. As we continue to improve and develop Ideal808.com, our privacy policy may be altered at any given time. Please use this page as a reference for the most current details regarding our online policies.

### Website and Information Security

All of your online credit card transactions are completely secured with Ideal808.com. This website uses Secure Socket Layering (SSL), the industry-standard encryption technology that ensures safe internet transmissions of your personal information. If you prefer to purchase by phone, please call 808.847.6000, Monday - Saturday, 3:00 pm - 11:00 pm EST (Eastern Standard Time). One of our customer care associates will be more than glad to assist you.

### Usage of Information

We will collect information for the usage of:

  * Completing your purchase transactions.
  * Keeping you informed about the status order.
  * Providing the services you requested.
  * Sending you our catalogs and other promotions via e-mail.
  * Improving our merchandise selections, customer service, and overall shopping experiences.

### Sharing of Your Information

All customer information is kept strictly confidential and shall not be shared or bartered with in any way with another company other than, Ideal808.com.

### Your Account and Membership

To maximize your shopping experience we ask that all shoppers register with Ideal808.com. by storing your information on our secure server, you will only have to enter your e-mail address and password to have access and ability to add, delete, or change information under your account. By using Ideal808.com services, you are to take responsibility for the safety of your password and using it on our website. You agree to take responsibility for any activity that takes place under your account or password. - Children (people under the age of 18): Ideal808.com does not sell to children, unless accompanied by the parent or guardian who will buy on behalf of the person under 18 years of age. We are under the impression that any order receive are by an adult or accompanying parent or guardian.

### Promotional Emails...“Spam”

\- Members benefits such as promotional emails are sent only if you have requested to receive them. Should you decide at a latter date that you no longer want to receive such promotional emails, simply click on the link at the bottom of the e-mail received to complete your request.

### Cookies and Browser Settings

In order to be able to use our online shopping cart system, you will need to have cookies enabled in your web browser. This will allow you view and access your member information and other secured pages. To set you browser cookie settings, find your browser’s internet options or privacy section settings, and set your privacy setting to Medium.

### Termination

\- Our Privacy Policies and Terms of Service are effective unless terminated by either you or Ideal808.com. You may terminate this Agreement at any time, provided that you discontinue any further use of this web site. You are personally liable for any orders placed or charges incurred through your account prior to termination. Ideal808.com reserves the right to change, suspend, or discontinue all or any aspect of this Web Site at any time without notice. * We reserve the right to change, modify or amend our policies at any given time. Please check our Privacy Policies page periodically for any changes.
